Have your injuries improved
any, Avdol? They have.
As relieved as I am.
I'm even more relieved
knowing you're alright.
Yes, well, I'm fortunate there was
no significant damage to my cornea.
I'm expected to make a full recovery.
This takes me back to middle school.
During what should have
been an ordinary game,
one of my classmates took
a baseball to the eye.
He was good as new the next day.
And as it turned out, his eye
had only lost a bit of fluid.
Wait, are you serious?
No.
I'll get these bandages off in no time,
and I'll catch up with you in a few days.
In 800 kilometers are Cairo and Dio.
Everyone, you must remain vigilant.
Now let's see.
What kind of language is this
hospital bill written in anyway?
I guess it's supposed to be Arabic,
but man, if this crap isn't confusing.
The zero is a five, the decimal
is a zero, and the seven is a six.
And what the heck is this wormy-looking
thingamajig supposed to be?
It's a four, so the amount we owe is...
46,350 Egyptian pounds!
That's insane!
Oh, my God!
What kind of dog is he?
He's so funny looking.
Look at that.
Why in the world is he chewing gum?
He must be waiting for someone.
Such a good little doggy.
And here I thought Iggy
was waiting for us outside.
Good grief.
Looks like he's a hit with the ladies.
Should we tell him doggies
don't usually chew gum?
What a peculiar little puppy.
Hello there, ladies.
Hmm?
Here's a little bit of
friendly advice for you girls.
Step away if you know what's good for you.
I know he comes across as a
charming furball at first,
but deep in his soul, he harbors
an extreme hatred for people.
If you're not careful
when you least expect...
What the hell are you doing?!
Get off of me, you damn mutt!
You're such a beauty!
Oh, you get along so well!
In your dreams, we don't get along at all.
Damn it, Iggy.
Would you get the hell off of me?
We'll catch you guys later.
See you, lovebirds. Mr.
Joestar, please help me.
Hey, hang on a minute, would you?
What the hell?
You nasty little mutt!
I don't know.
The end of the world.
Stop it now!
It's the end of the world.
I'm going to continue to walk.
The end of the world.
I'm going to go to the last page.
I'm going to go to the end of the world.
In ancient times,
Egyptians were in the habit of burying
their dead on the west bank of?
the Nile where the sun sets.
That's the reason Egyptian cities
stand on the east side of the Nile.
On the west side, however,
you're likely to find graves and
mortuary temples scattered about.
But our enemies don't
care about east or west.
They'll come from whatever
direction is most advantageous.
Look, I know you didn't ask for my opinion,
but your cows are far too lethargic.
Although they're strong,
I'll give them that.
Hey, Chaka!
Move your ass, boy!
And would you stop
dragging the rear already?
What a disgrace!
Some man you are!
How are you, my son?
Looks like your son and your
cow have something in common.
A sword?
What's something like this doing out here?
Hey, look!
It's a sword! Give me that!
Look at that.
Must have been dropped.
I can't believe no one's
come back to claim it.
Their loss is our gain, because this
sword is probably worth a fortune.
Hey, what if the owner's
still in the area?
Poor guy must be
panicking right about now.
On the off chance it's some
kind of fancy-schmancy artifact,
shouldn't we give it to the police?
You idiot!
This sword could be the end
of all of our money troubles!
But I'm the one who found it.
It won't be worth a damn
thing if it's blunt.
Pull it out so we can take a look.
Right.
What's wrong?
The damn thing won't budge.
Why the hell won't it come out?
That's weird.
Let me try it. Take it.
You hold this end. Right.
It's no use.
The blade hasn't moved
a single centimeter.
Father, let me have a go.
Oh, shut up!
If I can't free it, what chance
does an idiot like you have?
My hands!
What happened to my hand?
My hand!
Why is it spewing blood?
How the hell did the sword cut me?
We pulled on a damn thing, but
the blade wouldn't come out.
All I did was grab it by the hill.
There's something
strange about that sword.
Hey, you think now's a
good time for me to try?
You know what?
Fine.
Go ahead and try it if you want.
It came out so easy.
I didn't put the slightest
bit of effort into it.
What?
I can hear it.
This makes no sense.
I can hear the blade ringing.
I'm by no means an expert when it comes
to swords or things of that nature.
But I don't think I've ever
encountered a blade this beautiful.
It's like a rare Japanese katana.
It glistens like it's
cloaked in ice-cold water.
We've been graced with
an amazing discovery.
Hand it over, my boy!
I don't like you!
It has no business wielding
such a valuable treasure!
Oh, God! Sugar!
Why?
Why would you do this to your father?
I don't know what happens.
You were standing behind me,
and before I knew it, the sword!
It's not my fault, I swear!
Why are you just standing there?
We have to hurry and get him to
a doctor before it's too late!
This sword is evil!
It's almost as though the
blade has a mind of its own!
Be calm.
Still your heart, Chaka.
Their deaths mean nothing.
Nothing whatsoever, Chaka.
Just...
just who are you?
I can't see you, but
I can hear your voice.
I am the stand of the god
Anubis, ruler of the underworld,
deity of embalming, and lord of the dead.
You have unsheathed me, thus
you shall be my standings.
You are a virtuoso, so I shall
make you master of the world.
You shall wield me, and you shall kill.
Kill, kill, kill, kill.
Father and that man deserve to die, so
they should be thrilled that I killed them.
I think I'll hack you to
pieces while I'm on a roll.
Wait a minute, Chaka!
You don't really want to do this!
Please let me live, okay?
I don't want to die!
How the hell did he do that?
Somehow the cow's completely unharmed!
Slaughter Joseph, slice
Polnareff, cleave Jotaro in two.
You are a fighting genius,
a master of the sword.
No one in the world is
a match for your blade.
No one!
Come, Ambo.
Come on, do we really have time
to lounge around in this place?
Would you quit complaining?
They've been kind enough to
allow us passage on their ferry,
so we must show our respect.
I don't know about you guys, but I'm
starving, so let's get something to eat.
Wow, you never stop, do you?
Here, this should tide you over for now.
You know damn well that's eggies!
Would you just take the gum already?
Hey, where's the bathroom, huh?
Shall we look for it?
Hey, mister, over here!
Wanna buy some papyrus?
This papyrus is the original paper.
Want a piece of Egyptian history?
Here, take a look.
This is 100 % Bone Feet
papyrus. Papyrus, huh?
I'll give you a good price.
Are you positive this is the real thing?
Of course, my friend.
I'll have you know a famous Egyptian
craftsman drew this, so it's quite genuine.
This crap is fake and you know it.
If this were actual papyrus,
it wouldn't rip so easily.
I'm no fool.
You should try a little.
For the love of, where'd Mr.
Joestar and the others go?
Not was that Iggy?
Why, you get back here, you little butt!
Hey, what about my body?
Stupid dog.
He managed to get away.
Gotta say, if my hunch is correct, then
you've got a lot of balls, my friend.
Seems like you're planning to attack me
while we're in a crowd
of innocent bystanders.
Guys like you are a rare breed.
Stand users don't usually show themselves,
let alone face their attacker head-on.
It's kind of noble.
I didn't think you guys had that trait.
Tell me your name.
My name is Chaka,
and my stand is known as Anubis, the
one true ruler of the Underworld.
Now then, Jean-Pierre Polnareff,
prepare to surrender your life to me.
You want me to surrender my life?
Man, oh man, you sure don't
mince words, do you, Chaka?
If nothing else, your confidence is more
impressive than your other companions.
Give me your best shot.
Let's see if your Anubis stand
is all it's cracked up to be.
Come out, chariot!
He's brandishing his sword,
but is he really planning to fight
me with that instead of his stand?
Something's off.
His movements, his grip, his stance,
they're the dead giveaways of an amateur.
But that doesn't make sense.
I need to keep my distance from him!
What the hell is going on here?
His sword passed right
through the pillar and if
that wasn't enough he got
me without leaving even a
single tear in my shirt if
I hadn't stepped back when
I did I would have been
killed you bastard cheerios
damn it why don't you show yourself and
face me like a real fighter you coward
Merd.
This can't be happening.
I lost him.
He could be hiding behind
any one of these pillars.
Judging from his attacks, his sword
can pass through solid objects.
And unfortunately for me, my chariot's
striking range is only about one meter.
Damn it.
He's tougher than I thought he'd be.
I honestly can't believe
this asshole is actually
giving me a run for my
money in a sword fight.
But mark my words, you won't
have the upper hand for long.
Hey Chaka, are you listening?
I've got a nice fuse, so
let's see what you've got.
There's no way you can sneak up
on me if I'm not behind a pillar.
Unless you're planning on
popping out of the ground.
Ha ha ha!
What the…
He's behind the pillar!
My sword doesn't need
to pass through objects!
With the power of this blade I
can cut through the pillar itself!
Now die, Pondarest!
Man, that was a close one.
That technique is so secret that
not even Jotaro knows about it.
Silver Chariot can launch its rapier.
The downside is I only get one shot.
My opponent dodges I'm history.
A last resort once I've
exhausted my other options.
While it's true I didn't kill you,
I highly doubt you'll be getting
back up for another round.
Huh?
That's peculiar.
How the heck did it get
back into its scabbard?
Did it slip in by chance?
I didn't notice before,
but now that I see it up close, I
fully appreciate the sword's beauty.
I have to unsheathe it.
Hey there, Polnareff.
Thought we'd lost you.
We were worried when you up
and vanished by yourself.
We thought you'd been
ambushed by the enemy.
Wait, are you okay?
Huh?
Oh, it's you, Mr. Joestar.
I'm so fuzzy, I can't think straight.
Maybe it's from being tossed around.
My injuries are worse than I thought.
Polnareff, why are you
squatting like that?
You didn't step in poop, did you?
Polnareff, how did you
come across that sword?
Did something happen out here?
Yeah, I had a showdown with
some dirtbag that attacked me.
What?
An enemy stand user?
It's all over now.
He said his stand was
known as the god Anubis.
It was able to literally
phase through objects and
cut them once it had a
target in its crosshairs.
He was a strong foe.
But despite his formidable power,
when all was said and done,
he was no match for the likes of
me, Polnareff reassured himself.
He was using this sword as his way.
Where did it go?
Where'd those rats come from?
And why are they making off of the sword?
Get out of here!
Jeez, talk about creepy.
No one told me even the rats
steal stuff in this place.
If you guys want to steal
something, steal some cheese.
Yeah that's unusual.
The sword stuck in the scabbard.
It's jammed in here really tight.
Hey Polnareff.
While I'm relieved that you're all right,
don't ever run off by yourself again.
Got it.
It's dangerous.
The enemy will find a way to attack you
even if you're just alone for a few seconds.
Oh crap. I forgot.
That's the sound of our ship taking off.
Without us, we need to
hurry and get on board.
We're
heading to Edfa today.
What?
Come on guys, wait for me.
Polnareff, so you decided to bring
the sword with you after all.
Yeah, I'm gonna turn it in to the police.
This thing is a dangerous
weapon, you know.
Hmm, that's a good plan.
Anyone could pick it up at those
ruins, so we can't take any chances.
It's probably worth a small fortune.
Quiet, Iggy.
You can't make noise in here.
If you keep this up,
we can get kicked out.
What the hell is wrong
with that mutt today?
Ah, well, since the
damn dog won't shut up,
I guess I'll just take
the sword to the cops now.
Polnareff, weren't you?
listening when we told you not to go off!
on your own?
Seriously, we talked about this earlier.
Jotaro, tag along and keep
him out of trouble, would ya?
Gotcha.
Hey, shouldn't our first stop
have been the police station?
Oh, take it easy, Jotaro.
A man's got to look his absolute
best, as the saying goes.
Oh, before I forget.
Old man, you mind putting this
over there out of the way?
Sure.
That thing's a dangerous weapon.
All right, back to what
I was saying earlier.
I did a fair amount of rolling around
and ended up getting kind of dirty.
Make this face gorgeous
again, Mr. Barber. Will do.
Ow!
Hey, would you watch it?
In case you haven't
noticed, that razor's dull.
Come on, Mr.
Barber, sharpen that thing.
This is supposed to be the most
relaxing part of the haircut.
Good grief, you're such a prima donna.
You're right sir.
My apologies
Oh, better.
Much better.
Now that's a shave, Mr.
Barber.
That's what I'm talking about.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear it.
Tre Bone, barber.
Tre Bone, man.
And now, if you wouldn't
mind getting under my chin.
Sure.
Right here.
Under your chin, yes. Huh?
You did say under your
chin, right, Polnareff?
What the hell?
Remember me, you fool?
I'm the Anubistan, and this
time you're going to die!
Thank you.
The sword is the stand!
I won't lose twice to the same adversary.
This guy's strong.
The more we fight this
stand, the faster it gets.
His eyes that stare.
This time, I'll take your head!